3. Opens the browser of choice: Chrome, Firefox or Edge
9. Driver opened by Katalon is used in Selenium from this step.
15. This step takes the Query from input excel and fetches data from Neo4j database.
Saves the results from neo4j and application in the same name mentioned in the input excel.
21. Clicks on the Cases button in the Navbar of ICDC's homepage.
27. Clicks on the Filter 'Study' from left pane
33. Selects the specific check box from 'Study' filter.
39. Selects the specific check box from 'Study' filter.
45. Reads the results displayed for the selected filter (from all the pages) and saves in the excel mentioned in Input file
51. Reads Neo4j DB using the query from Input file and saves the data in the excel mentioned in Input file
57. Reads Neo4j excel and Webdata excel as lists and compares the data.